<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Banglore Crime News</string>
    <string name="crime_news">Banglore Mirror</string>
    <string name="img_banglore_mirror">img_banglore_mirror</string>
    <string name="headlines">Headlines</string>
    <string name="description">Description</string>
    <string name="hint">Two of a three-member gang that had decided to shift to robbery as the agency where they worked was shut ever since the lockdown came into place were caught in their very first attempt at the criminal venture.The three men had managed to rob a mobile tower technician, but the victim got the help of a few passersby and managed to chase and nab two of the accused near Vegahalli Cross on Bengaluru-Chintamani Road on Tuesday. Mobile tower technician M Goutham, a resident of Chokkanahalli in Bengaluru rural district, had gone to fill diesel in the generators of the mobile towers off Old Madras Road. As he was returning, three men on a scooter accosted him and blocked the way for his car. They demanded money from him. When Goutham refused to give money, the men pulled him out of the car and robbed him of cash. Goutham raised an alarm and two passersby, identified as Charan Kumar and Srinivas, rushed to help. “Looking at passersby rushing towards them, the accused tried to escape on their scooter. The victim and the two others chased them and managed to catch two of the three along with their scooter. The two were then brought to the police station and have been handed over. During interrogation, the accused claimed that they were running short of money due to lockdown and so had tried to rob people,” said an officer. The accused who were nabbed and handed over to the police are S Mahendra Reddy, 26, of Chittoor in Andhra Pradesh, and A Fayaz Pasha, 24, of Chikkaballapura. The accused who managed to escape is identified as V Bagavalla Srinivasa, 36, of Andhra Pradesh. The two accused were said to have been working as drivers in a travel agency and did not have any work ever since the lockdown. The police have recovered the cash and the scooter from the accused worth around Rs 50,000. Police believe even the scooter was stolen. A case of robbery under section 392 of the IPC has been registered against the three and a search is on for the accused who escaped.</string>
</resources>
